https://americansforprosperity.org/privacy-policy/

Please select your state so that we can show you the most relevant content. Select State...AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoFloridaGeorgiaIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNationalNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaPennsylvaniaSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWest VirginiaWisconsin Americans for Prosperity Select State...AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoFloridaGeorgiaIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNationalNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaPennsylvaniaSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWest VirginiaWisconsinNewsroomTake ActionDonateAbout
MoreThe IssuesScorecardCareersContact Us Menu Select State...AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoFloridaGeorgiaIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNationalNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaPennsylvaniaSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWest VirginiaWisconsinNewsroomTake ActionDonateAboutThe IssuesScorecardCareersContact UsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY (the “Organization”) recognizes that visitors to our respective Web sites /websites, web properties, and mobile applications are entitled to know how we collect, use, and maintain information we collect or may collect about them.
This privacy policy explains what information we collect, how we use that information, with whom we will share this information, and related information. As used in this Policy, the terms “web site” or “site” include any Americans for Prosperity mobile application, whether or not explicitly stated.Information CollectionNon-Personally Identifiable Information  We gather certain broad information about Web site use, including the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the programs and services preferred.  We look at the data in summary form, rather than on an individual basis.  We gather this information so we can learn how many people visit our site, see which pages are the most and least viewed, identify which Web sites are referring visitors to our site, and related information.  The data helps us determine the extent to which visitors use certain parts of our Web site.  Thus, we use this information to help us in restructuring our site to better meet the needs of our constituency and to better serve our constituency as an effective organization. In connection with these activities we may use some of the below mentioned tools.
Cookies We use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how the site is used.  Cookies are small strings of text stored on your computer’s hard drive by a Web server.  We use session cookies to identify your computer during a particular session, i.e., when you sign into the site or post a comment.  If you create a user account or otherwise join our site, these cookies enable you to store your password for fast logon and other conveniences.  We do not store personal or sensitive information in cookies.  Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address.  Most Web browsers provide you the ability to accept or decline cookies, as well as to be warned each time a cookie is being sent.  If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to take advantage of all aspects of our site.
IP Addresses We collect and analyze traffic on our Web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors.  An IP address is the unique numeric identifier assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet.  An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally.  However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.
Personally Identifiable Information Certain actions and areas of the site require you to provide personal information, including but not limited to:Join our Web site or create a user account;Submit a comment;Make a donation;Contact a legislator;Join an exclusive strategy phone call;Obtain a premium gift; orSign a petition.The personal information we collect may consist of your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, birth year, t-shirt size, hat size, and personal statement or similar information.  By submitting personal information to us, you agree that we may use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. We will update this privacy policy as we deem necessary.  You should be sure to reread this policy in its entirety from time to time. If you do submit information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted.  For instance, if you join our Web site and ask to be placed on our e-mail list, we will use your email address to send you alerts and other messages about topics and developments we think may be of interest to you.   Likewise, for any web-based grassroots program, we may collect and use personally identifiable information in connection with such grassroots outreach and advocacy efforts.  In order to use these grassroots that may allow us to send e-mails, faxes, or letters to policy makers, we may require a user to provide a name, mailing address, and e-mail address.  Information collected is used for the promotion of AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY’S legislative goals, grassroots outreach and policy advocacy.We may also use your information in other ways, such as to contact you about other activities and/or fundraising campaigns or as otherwise disclosed to you at the point of collection, and we may share or transfer your information with our affiliates and partners and any other organizations or entities for similar purposes.  Additionally, to the extent required by applicable federal or state law, we will provide this information to others.  To be clear, we may share personally and non-personally identifiable information with third parties that help manage our Web site and databases as well as with our partners, affiliates, or other third parties. You should be aware that we use third-party vendors to provide services on this site and in our offline business operations.  The information that you submit on this site may be provided to those vendors on a confidential basis so that those vendors can provide services (including, but not limited to, maintaining our databases, sending e-mail messages to our visitors, facilitating our fundraising activities and campaigns, or processing credit card donations) on our behalf.We also reserve the right to share personal information you provide with legal authorities if it is, in our sole opinion, necessary to investigate, prevent, or otherwise take action regarding suspected fraud, situations involving threats or potential harm, or if otherwise required by law (such as by a subpoena, court order, or other legal means).  In the event that we reasonably believe that you have violated any of the Terms of Conditions governing your use of this site, we reserve the right to use any information we have collected about you in connection with any efforts we make or made by any of our agents on our behalf.Financial Information You Choose to Provide If you choose to make an online donation, you will have to provide your credit card billing information.  Whenever this information is collected and transferred over the Internet to our secure server, it is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, the industry standard security technology that is designed to protect sensitive information.  Whenever we allow online donations, our online donation page will display a third party secure site seal to assure you that our Web site is authentic and that all transactions are secured by SSL encryption.  If you make a donation, the credit card information that you provide at the time of donation will be used only to process your donation and will not be used for any other purposes.Information about othersWe may access, collect, and store personal information about other people that is available to us through your contact list and/or address book. The website and mobile app allows users to complete contact information for entries on their contact list/address book, match their information with information available from other sources, and identify issues of interest. To revoke your consent for this access, you can change the settings on your device if that option is available, delete your profile, or delete or uninstall the mobile app from your device.Online Advertisements From time to time, we may run online advertisements on third-party Web sites to attract visitors to our site or to alert our supporters to special opportunities.  Our advertising partners may use cookies and clear GIFs on this site and on the third-party sites on which our ads appear, which allow the advertising partner to track certain information about user behavior, such as “click-stream data.”  Any use of information by an advertising partner would be governed by their terms of use and privacy policy, so be sure to be familiar with these policies prior to responding to online advertisements.Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions From time to time, we may request information from you via online polls, surveys, sweepstakes, or contests.  Participation in these polls, surveys, sweepstakes, or contests is completely voluntary; you have a choice whether or not to disclose information required to enter.  Information requested may include personal contact information such as your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information.  Contact information will be used to notify winners, award prizes, and contact users with further information about AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY, as well as the products and services of AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY’S partners and third parties.  Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving use and satisfaction of the AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY site and to better the organization’s accomplishment of its’ mission.  In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates, partners, and other organizations or entities.E-mail Newsletter and Updates  If you sign up to receive our e-mail newsletter and updates, we may collect, store, and use your e-mail address to send you such information from AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  We may also collect and store other personally identifiable information including but not limited to your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information you may opt to provide us.  If you provide us with your mobile phone number, we may use it to send you text messages from AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates, partners, and other organizations or entities.Text messages  If you sign up to receive text messages from us, we will collect, store and use your mobile phone number to send you such messages from AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  We will also collect and store other personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information you may opt to provide to us.  If you provide us with your e-mail address, we will use it to send you e-mail newsletters and updates from AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates, partners, and other organizations or entities.
User Accounts If you sign up for a user account, to participate in any Web site features we offer, we will collect and store certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information you may opt to provide to us.  Your user account information will be visible to designated team members of AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY and our third-party Web site services vendor, but not to other registered users or Web site visitors (except to the extent you voluntarily provide any such information when you post your comments).  When you register for a user account, you will also be registered to receive e-mail updates, e-mail newsletters, and text messages as a member of AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates, partners, and other organizations or entities.
User Comments  Please be aware that any personal information you provide in connection with comments you contribute to this site or any other interactive features we may offer will be visible to other users and Web site visitors.
User Letters and Articles If you use any interactive forms we may offer to draft articles or letters to officials, editors, or other recipients, we will collect and store certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information you may opt to provide to us.  We will use this information to help you draft your article or letter, and to send you e-mail updates, e-mail newsletters, and text messages as a member of AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.  In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates, partners, and other organizations or entities.
Job Opportunities You may choose to apply for employment or an internship position with our affiliate AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY FOUNDATION through online application forms we may provide or by sending us, by e-mail or otherwise, a resume and letter (containing personally identifiable information).  Any information you provide to us in this regard will be viewed by AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY FOUNDATION only for the purpose of evaluating your application and/or responding to your employment-related inquiry.
Other Communications  You may choose to contact AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY, by e-mail or otherwise, with other inquiries or to provide comments.  Any personally identifiable information you provide in connection with such inquiries or comments will be collected and used by AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY for the purpose of processing and responding to your inquiries or comments. Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, and Other Third-Party Social Networking Sites The Organization maintains an active presence on several social networks.  Any information we collect from you on those sites will be governed by the privacy policies governing those social networks.  Except as prohibited by those sites, we will use any personally identifiable information we collect from or about you from those sites in the manner described in this Policy.
Security Information submitted via the Internet, including through a Web page or e-mail is subject to interception or incorrect routing, and the Internet is not a fully secure communications channel.  Please consider this prior to submitting any information to us via this Web site. Certain sections of this site may have heightened security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information you have provided.  The security measures used on this site to protect any available online donation pages include, but are not limited to, industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, third party SSL certificate validation, firewalls, and internal policies to maintain the security of stored data.  While we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Your Help Is Needed Remember, breaches of security also can occur when users are not vigilant in protecting their own information.  The next section of our privacy policy suggests some actions you can take to help control the security of your personal informationAlthough we do our best to protect your privacy on our site, we need your help.You have control over your own privacy.  Think carefully before providing any personal or financial information online.Although this site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information you provide, no e-mail or Web transmission is completely secure against interception.  If you are worried because your communication is very sensitive, do not send it electronically.When you write to us or send us submissions, if you desire to remain anonymous, you should not tell us your name, the names of other users, or of your friends.  To fully protect your privacy, you should try to exclude any information that you think may identify you or others.Remember that we cannot protect your privacy once you leave our site, such as by hyperlink.  So when you visit other Web sites, check each site’s privacy policy, and be careful about the information you submit or share.You should be aware that in some areas of this site we utilize personalization measures designed to make your site experience more enjoyable (i.e., personalized links in e-mail that allow data fields to be pre-populated with certain personal information).  We need your help to protect the information embedded in these links.  You should always keep your e-mail account information secure and not allow others to access your e-mail account.In addition, you should only forward our email messages or other Web site information (such as volunteer or job postings) to others through the buttons or links provided within the e-mail or Web site.  When you use your e-mail system’s forwarding capabilities, others may be able to take actions in your name and/or access your personal information. You may be given the option to turn on a persistent cookie on your computer.  Remember that once you have set a persistent cookie that is linked to your personal information, anyone can access your personal information by using your computer.In addition to the records left on your computer by cookies, your browser and operating system contain other records of your Web browsing and other actions (e.g., browser history).  As with cookies, you can find information about how to clear these history trails in your browser’s “Help” section or through other Web sites that provide detailed information for each browser and operating system.How to Unsubscribe or Contact Us About Your Information If you do not want to receive any e-mail from us in the future, click the “unsubscribe” reference in any e-mail we send you. If you would like to opt-out of postal mail, please share your address and preference in the brief form below. Otherwise, you may email info@afphq.org to complete the opt-out process, or send a letter to the below address requesting that we unsubscribe you from our contact lists. Note that absent a specific request your records will remain in our database, but your log-in and e-mail address will be deactivated.Direct Mail Opt-Out RequestName*
First
Last Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific State
ZIP Code Please remove me from...*
Donation Requests - Postal Mail
Policy Alerts - Postal MailCommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
If you wish to review the contact information we have on file for you, correct your contact information, provide a change of address, or inform us how you wish your contact information to be used, please contact our staff. You may contact us by mail, e-mail, or telephone, as follows: Americans for Prosperity 1310 N Courthouse Road, Ste 700 Arlington, VA 22201 Phone: (703) 224-3200 Attn: Online Content Manager Email: info@afphq.org Policy Last Updated: September 1, 2016
Modifications to this Privacy Policy We reserve the right to amend or change this Policy at any time.  In the event of any material change, AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY will post a prominent notice of such a revision to this Policy on this site’s home page or e-mail you such notice at an e-mail address you have provided to AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY.
Complaints or Questions If you have any questions or concerns about how we have used information we have collected about you, please contact us: Compliance Officer Americans for Prosperity 1310 N. Courthouse Road, Ste 700 Arlington, VA 22201 info@afphq.org (Put “Compliance Officer” in subject line)
AboutPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseLegacy GivingCareers Select State...AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoFloridaGeorgiaIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNationalNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaPennsylvaniaSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWest VirginiaWisconsin© 2020 AMERICANS FOR PROSPERITY. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.1310 N. Courthouse Rd. – Suite 700 – Arlington, VA 22201General: 703-224-3200 | Press: 703-224-3177
